Choppy trade continues as the Nifty gives up
gains to hover around the lowest point of the
session below the 25700 mark. Broader indices
however stay in the positive territory. Metals
and PSU banks remain resilient while IT, auto
and real estate stocks stay under pressure.
ICICI Lombard delivered strong premium
growth and market share gains in Q3,
but profitability took a hit due to
higher claims costs and one-time labor
code impact. ICICI credential life meanwhile
saw brokerages turn constructive on margins.
Inforce is expected to report a modest
sequential revenue growth and largely
stable margins with constant currency
growth slowing despite currency tailwinds.
Investors will track commentary on tech spending,
pricing pressure, and enterprise AI adoption.
December WPI data edged up to 0.83% reversing
the deflationary print of a third of a percent
lower in November. The data came in well
above street expectations. The rebound is
being largely attributed to base effects and
a pickup in food and global commodity prices.
Indian rail railways may seek up to a
10% hike in capital outlay this budget
with a sharp focus on safety, capacity
expansion and private participation. Big
ticket priorities include funding for
the Kawatch train protection system,
new rail tracks and state
and station redevelopment.